<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.synchrosonic.SynchroSonic</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>SynchroSonic</name>
  <summary>Linux-first LAN audio casting and receiver control</summary>
  <developer id="io.github.udayasri0">
    <name>UdayaSri0</name>
  </developer>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.synchrosonic.SynchroSonic.desktop</launchable>
  <provides>
    <binary>synchrosonic-app</binary>
  </provides>
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/UdayaSri0/AudioShare</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/UdayaSri0/AudioShare/issues</url>
  <releases>
    <release version="0.1.11" date="2026-04-24">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Aligned release metadata and packaging documentation for SynchroSonic v0.1.11.</li>
          <li>Rechecked Linux release artifact expectations for AppImage, Debian, Flatpak, and tarball outputs.</li>
          <li>Corrected stale version references from earlier release preparation passes.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.1.10" date="2026-04-16">
      <description>
        <p>
          Linux packaging polish and metadata alignment update for the
          SynchroSonic desktop app.
        </p>
        <p>
          This release keeps the packaging, documentation, and release-facing
          metadata aligned on version 0.1.10, expands the documented Linux
          package targets, and describes preview-only runtime paths more
          honestly.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <description>
    <p>
      SynchroSonic is a Linux-first GTK4/libadwaita desktop application for
      capturing system audio, discovering receivers, casting over the local
      network, running a receiver mode, and inspecting stream, sync, and buffer
      health.
    </p>
    <p>
      The current release track focuses on Linux PipeWire tooling, LAN
      transport, and explicit diagnostics. Bluetooth support is intentionally
      limited to selecting local Linux playback outputs exposed by PipeWire.
    </p>
    <p>
      The current public release line uses version 0.1.11 and the canonical
      AudioShare GitHub repository for source, releases, and issue tracking.
    </p>
  </description>
  <categories>
    <category>AudioVideo</category>
    <category>Audio</category>
    <category>Network</category>
  </categories>
  <keywords>
    <keyword>audio</keyword>
    <keyword>streaming</keyword>
    <keyword>lan</keyword>
    <keyword>pipewire</keyword>
    <keyword>receiver</keyword>
    <keyword>casting</keyword>
  </keywords>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
</component>
